okay so the food stamps are being cut off um there's gonna be no food stamps for november
i know people are struggling i'm gonna remind y'all of the resource that i give out to people
all the time y'all see me post about it a million times but people always miss it and ask me if i
can repost it this is gonna be a repost of this month i will probably repost this a number of
times findhelp.org one second findhelp.org is a website where you can go type in your zip code
and you can find food pantries and a host of other resources i accidentally clicked emergency food
here so ignore that but if you go down to uh food and then you click on click on food pantries it's
gonna verify if you're a human but then you will have a list of local food pantries this is uh the
zip code i put in was my old one from baltimore but like literally any zip code should work find your
local food pantry like give to your local food pantry i'm gonna like uh be giving shopping for
some canned goods later to give and some non-perishable goods to give to a couple of my
local food pantries um right now we need each other more than ever this is your reminder to uh share this
resource um but yeah uh it's gonna be a little sticky in these next couple of uh months truly but
i do think if we stick together we'll be good that's it uh i will probably do a can drive
so look out for that i just have to figure out logistics but we need to help each other that's it